import { CardDto } from "@/dto/Card.dto";

const Cards: CardDto = [
  {
    id: "1",
    front: "What is 2 + 2?",
    back: "4",
  },
  {
    id: "2",
    front: "What is 2 + 3?",
    back: "5",
  },
  {
    id: "3",
    front: "What is 2 + 4?",
    back: "6",
  },
  {
    id: "4",
    front: "What is 2 + 5?",
    back: "7",
  },
  {
    id: "5",
    front: "What is 2 + 6?",
    back: "8",
  },
  {
    id: "6",
    front: "What is 2 + 7?",
    back: "9",
  },
  {
    id: "7",
    front: "What is 2 + 8?",
    back: "10",
  },
  {
    id: "8",
    front: "What is 2 + 9?",
    back: "11",
  },
  {
    id: "9",
    front: "What is 2 + 10?",
    back: "12",
  },
  {
    id: "10",
    front: "What is 2 + 11?",
    back: "13",
  },
  {
    id: "11",
    front: "What is 2 + 12?",
    back: "14",
  },
];
